Have joined us.  Let's
connect with them and talk to them.  Aniket Sarkar is
associated with us.  Aniket Hi Good
afternoon.  Tell me which stock do
you want advice on?
Hello, yes I have 900 shares of ICICI
Lobert General Insurance which I have
bought for long term.  I need opinion on that.
Ok.  The quantity you have is 900 and the
entry price is 1800.  Ok.
Yes.
Ok.  Let's take some advice on this.
Ajit ji, he has ICICI LBAD.
He has bought 900 shares at the price of Rs 1800.  I have a slightly
long term view and the current price is
1823, I think
they have bought it around that time.
He bought it around this time.  What
will be your perspective?
Look, no doubt volatility in the insurance space has been
experienced a lot
across life insurance and general
insurance counters.  But ICICI GI
is a comparatively better structure.  Meaning, you
saw a retracement from the record high,
from around 2200 you came to the levels of 1680 and as far as
I can see,
in the last one and a quarter years, you are seeing trading in the same band from 2000 to 1600.
Because their buying price is
near the current levels.  There is a long term view.
I think it should remain that way.  As of now the
1600 level is holding.  Till now
no major damage is visible
in the structure.  The overall consolidation will
remain with a positive bias.  The actual growth will happen
around 2050.  In that case,
you will again see the stock moving towards a new high.
So right now the opinion would be to hold
for long term with a stop loss of 1600.
You have to hold for now with a stop loss of 1600.
This is the opinion you are getting.